Guide to the Vassar College Alumnae/i Biographical Files (AAVC), circa 1865-2015
Archives and Special Collections Library, Vassar College Libraries
- Class of 1904
  - Kuhn, Adelina (Box 19)
  - Ladd, Elizabeth T. (Box 19)
  - Lauder, Estelle A. (Box 19)
  - Lee, E. Louise (Box 19)
  - LeFevre, Elizabeth (Box 19)
  - Lemon, Jeanette L. (Box 19)
  - Leonard, Lora E. (Box 19)
  - Long, Margaret B. (Box 19)
  - Lowe, Jessie Alida (Box 19)
  - Lyon, Dorothy D. (Box 19)
  - MacRobert, Edna A. (Box 19)
  - Marten, M. Lillian (Box 19)
  - McCain, Bess N. (Box 19)
  - McCain, Milla M. (Box 19)
  - McCandless, Faith I. (Box 19)
  - McKinnon, Maude (Box 19)
  - Menner, Mary A. (Box 19)
  - Merrell, Katharine S. (Box 19)
  - Millard, Ethel F. (Box 19)
  - Millspaugh, May B. (Box 19)
  - Moore, Edith R. (Box 19)
  - Morenus, Eugenie M. (Box 19)
  - Munn, Theodora (Box 19)
  - Murphy, Elinor (Box 19)
  - Murphy, Jessie I. (Box 19)
  - Napier, Edith L. (Box 19)
  - Neely, Myra Idell (Box 19)
  - Nims, Virginia E. (Box 19)
  - Norris, Martha E. (Box 19)
  - O’Shaughnessy, May (Box 19)
  - Owen, Nancy W. (Box 19)
  - Page, Edna O. (Box 19)
  - Parton, Elizabeth W. (Box 19)
  - Patch, Edith R. (Box 19)
  - Pelton, Florence (Box 19)
  - Perry, Jeannette (Box 19)
  - Platt, Edith (Box 19)
  - Plumb, Ethel (Box 19)
  - Powell, Mary Dudley (Box 19)
  - Price, Clara E. (Box 19)
  - Rich, Anna L. (Box 19)
  - Riedell, Elizabeth (Box 19)
  - Rudyard, Charlotte L. (Box 19)
  - Russel, Julie R. (Box 19)
  - Russell, Susan C. (Box 19)
  - Sebring, Helen A. (Box 19)
  - Sessions, Sara Mabel (Box 19)
  - Sherwood, Isabel S. (Box 19)
  - Smith, Alice E. (Box 19)
  - Smith, Marguerite S. (Box 19)
  - Smith, Natalie Lord (Box 19)
  - Smith, Stella M. (Box 19)
  - Smith, Winifred (Box 19)
  - Stafford, Alice H. (Box 19)
  - Stanwood, Mabel (Box 19)
  - Steams, Anna P. (Box 19)
  - Steeves, Miriam (Box 19)
  - Stevenson, Margaretta P. (Box 19)
  - Stimson, Lucile H. (Box 19)
  - Stone, Pauline (Box 19)
  - Studley, Helen E. (Box 19)
  - Swetland, Velma Idella (Box 19)
  - Tallman, Lavinia (Box 19)
  - Taylor, Jeannette S. (Box 19)
  - Taylor, Lea Demarest (Box 19)
  - Taylor, Mary (Box 19)
  - Thomas, Margaret (Box 19)
  - Thompson, Mary T. (Box 19)
  - Thurston, Olive G. (Box 19)
  - Truax, Marjorie L. (Box 19)
  - True, Helen E. (Box 19)
  - Turnbull, Belle (Box 19)
  - Van Deusen, Marjorie H. (Box 19)
  - Van Riper, Cornelia Z. (Box 19)
  - Voorhees, Jeanne A. (Box 19)
  - Voorhees, Marian R. (Box 19)
  - Wakeman, Ethel S. (Box 19)
  - Waring, Dora (Box 19)
  - Warn, Amy L. (Box 19)
  - Warren, Constance (Box 19)
  - Waterbury, Norma R. (Box 19)
  - Waterman, E. Phoebe (Box 19)
  - Welch, Cora D. (Box 20)
  - Welch, Emily H. (Box 20)
  - Welles, Harriet C. (Box 20)
  - Welty, Ethel E. (Box 20)
  - Wheeler, Isabel (Box 20)
  - White, Ellen M. (Box 20)
  - Whiteside, Ida (Box 20)
  - Wilson, Pearl C. (Box 20)
  - Winans, Florence (Box 20)
  - Winchester, Frances (Box 20)
  - Wood, Annie W. (Box 20)
  - Wood, Helen C. (Box 20)
  - Wood, Lillian A. (Box 20)
  - Worcester, Abigail K. (Box 20)
  - Woodruff, Violet S. (Box 20)
  - Wyckoff, Alice F. (Box 20)
  - Wylie, Isabel C. (Box 20)
  - Yost, Mary (Box 20)
- Class of 1905
  - Abbott, Grace V. D. (Box 20)
  - Alexander, Helen (Box 20)
  - Angell, Sarah C. (Box 20)
  - Armsby, Caroline L. (Box 20)
  - Atkins, Lillian W. (Box 20)
  - Babson, Helen C. (Box 20)
  - Badeau, A. Marie (Box 20)
  - Ballard, Gertrude I. (Box 20)
  - Ballou, Margaret A. (Box 20)
  - Bals, Bertha A. (Box 20)
  - Bancroft, Helen C. (Box 20)
  - Barber, Helen C. (Box 20)
  - Barden, Bertha R. (Box 20)
  - Barkley, Florence M. (Box 20)
  - Barnes, Caroline S. (Box 20)
  - Barrere, Mary B. (Box 20)
  - Bass, Louise R. (Box 20)
  - Beirmeister, Sara Y. (Box 20)
  - Bell, Alma W. (Box 20)
  - Bell, Berta A. (Box 20)
  - Bell, Edith C. (Box 20)
  - Bell, Fanny A. (Box 20)
  - Bergen, Gertrude (Box 20)
  - Bethune, Ora (Box 20)
  - Blount, Elizabeth M. (Box 20)
  - Bon, Mary B. (Box 20)
  - Botsford, Elizabeth S. (Box 20)
  - Bradley, Lucy S. (Box 20)
  - Bradshaw, Agnes B. (Box 20)
  - Brezee, Edna W. (Box 20)
  - Briggs, Ethel J. (Box 20)
  - Brown, Gladys C. (Box 20)
  - Buffinton, Sylvia D. (Box 20)
  - Burlingame, Helen L. (Box 20)
  - Burrell, M. Elizabeth (Box 20)
  - Bussey, Irene W. (Box 20)
  - Butler, Elsa M. (Box 20)
  - Butler, Katharine W. (Box 20)
  - Cannon, Frances W. (Box 20)
  - Capron, Florence E. (Box 20)
  - Chapple, Mary L. (Box 20)
  - Chase, Margaret (Box 20)
  - Clark, H. Emma (Box 20)
  - Clarke, Julia (Box 20)
  - Clinton, Helen E. (Box 20)
  - Cochran, Anne E. (Box 20)
  - Cole, Eva M. (Box 20)
  - Collins, Edana S. (Box 20)
  - Collins, Eva (Box 20)
  - Colwell, Elizabeth W. (Box 20)
  - Comstock, Elizabeth M. (Box 20)
  - Conger, Mary R. (Box 20)
  - Copeland, A. May (Box 20)
  - Copley, Irene Shepard (Box 20)
  - Cummings, Alice J. (Box 20)
  - Curtis, Elizabeth E. (Box 20)
  - Cutler, Mary H. (Box 20)
  - Darrow, Georgiana F. (Box 20)
  - Day, Fanny E. (Box 20)
  - DeBevoise, Helen H. (Box 20)
  - DeLamater, Sarah M. (Box 20)
  - Delaney, Mary C. (Box 20)
  - Dinegan, Mary W. (Box 20)
  - Dolbeer, Florence B. (Box 20)
  - Dunbar, Margaret L. (Box 20)
  - Dunstan, Helen B. (Box 20)
  - Dutton, Louise E. (Box 20)
  - Eaton, Esther (Box 20)
  - Eddy, M. Eleanor (Box 20)
  - Eldred, Helena (Box 20)
  - Ellison, Beulah S. (Box 20)
  - Emmert, Varina (Box 20)
  - Evans, Elsie Louise (Box 20)
  - Falk, Stella M. (Box 20)
  - Fay, Agnes La F. (Box 20)
  - Fernald, Edith (Box 20)
  - Fleming, Margaret (Box 20)
  - Fletcher, Sara Eliza (Box 20)
  - Fontarede, Bertha A. (Box 20)
  - Forbes, Ruth (Box 20)
  - French, Katharine (Box 20)
  - Frenzel, Henrietta S. (Box 20)
  - Ganong, Edith W. (Box 20)
  - Gaylord, Anna E. (Box 20)
  - Gibson, Anna D. (Box 20)
  - Goff, Mary H. (Box 20)
  - Goldman, Edna G. (Box 20)
  - Greene, Mary E. (Box 20)
  - Griffis, Lillian E. (Box 20)
  - Guillaudeu, Florence D. (Box 20)
  - Hager, E. Mildred (Box 20)
  - Hague, Helen (Box 20)
  - Haines, Bertha P. (Box 20)
  - Haines, Marion E. (Box 20)
  - Halsey, Anna C. (Box 20)
  - Hamblen, Grace (Box 20)
  - Hamburg, Mabel J. (Box 20)
  - Hardick, Amy G. (Box 20)
  - Haring, Hazel H. (Box 20)
  - Hasbrouck, Olga (Box 20)
  - Hawley, Clara A. (Box 20)
  - Hazeltine, Fanny D. (Box 20)
  - Hedden, L. Josephine (Box 20)
  - Heinz, Zella F. (Box 20)
  - Hendrick, Helen (Box 20)
  - Henkel, Jessie R. (Box 20)
  - Henking, F. Adele (Box 20)
  - Henning, Martha (Box 20)
  - Herrick, Bertha (Box 20)
  - Heywood, Alice (Box 20)
  - Heywood, Rachel H. (Box 20)
  - Hickox, Laura C. (Box 20)
  - Hill, Ella L. (Box 20)
  - Hill, Helen (Box 20)
  - Hiscox, Marjorie (Box 20)
  - Hoag, Alice W. (Box 20)
  - Holden, Ethel R. (Box 20)
  - Holloway, Linda (Box 21)
  - Hopson, Elizabeth F. (Box 21)
  - Hopson, Helen T. (Box 21)
  - Howe, Florence A. (Box 21)
  - Hubbard, Stella R. (Box 21)
  - Hulbert, Adda B. (Box 21)
  - Hutchinson, Florence E. (Box 21)
  - Johns, Roberta T. (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Elizabeth M. (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Hazel (Box 21)
  - Johnson, Mary E. (Box 21)
  - Jones, Margaret M. (Box 21)
  - Josselyn, Bertha (Box 21)
  - Judson, Emily D. (Box 21)
  - Kavanagh, Mary I. (Box 21)
  - Kays, Amelia O. (Box 21)
  - Keeney, Ruth M. (Box 21)
  - Kelly, M. Elizabeth (Box 21)
  - Kelly, Molly S. (Box 21)
  - Kemble, Daisy E. (Box 21)
  - Kenyon, Helen (Box 21)
  - Kessel, Therese W. (Box 21)
  - King, Eleanor (Box 21)
  - Kingston, Mary I. (Box 21)
  - Kinsell, Vida R. (Box 21)
  - Kirkpatrick, Hazel (Box 21)
  - Knox, Mary L. (Box 21)
  - Lacey, Evelyn E. (Box 21)
  - Lancaster, Edith C. (Box 21)
  - Lane, Evelyn M. (Box 21)
  - Leavenworth, Helen L. (Box 21)
  - Lefevre, Blanche (Box 21)
  - Leonard, Evelyn (Box 21)
  - Lewis, Dorothy (Box 21)
  - Livermore, Elizabeth K. (Box 21)
  - Long, Mollie (Box 21)
  - Loomis, Kate S. (Box 21)
  - Loughridge, Alice E. (Box 21)
  - Lowenstein, Hilda B. (Box 21)
  - Lukens, Helen M. (Box 21)
  - Lyall, Agnes (Box 21)
  - Mack, Lura M. (Box 21)
  - Magie, Lucia T. (Box 21)
  - Manning, Harriet L. (Box 21)
  - Marshall, Elsie R. (Box 21)
  - Marshall, Lillie M. (Box 21)
  - Matthews, Jane A. (Box 21)
  - McCandless, Leora M. (Box 21)
  - McCarthy, Grace V. (Box 21)
  - McCloskey, Mildred (Box 21)
  - McCrelis, Jane B. (Box 21)
  - McCulloch, Ruth (Box 21)
  - McKinlay, Florence (Box 21)
  - McKisson, Ethel (Box 21)
  - McMichael, Bertha M. (Box 21)
  - McNaught, Grace I. (Box 21)
  - Mennen, Elma C. (Box 21)
  - Merselis, Ruth A. (Box 21)
  - Meserve, Alice W. (Box 21)
  - Meyer, Ella F. (Box 21)
  - Miles, Helen B. (Box 21)
  - Miller, Katie G. (Box 21)
  - Miller, Mona L. (Box 21)
  - Mills, Anna Rae (Box 21)
  - Moore, Mabel E. (Box 21)
  - Morehouse, Margaret (Box 21)
  - Morgan, Mary A. (Box 21)
  - Morgenthau, Helen (Box 21)
  - Mottley, Nan (Box 21)
  - Muckenhoupt, Loretta E. (Box 21)
  - Nichols, E. Marion (Box 21)
  - Norcross, Grace (Box 21)
  - Nutting, Helen C. (Box 21)
  - Ohr, Cerene (Box 21)
  - O’Loughlin, Evelyn G. (Box 21)
  - Ost, Ella H. (Box 21)
  - Overocker, Mary L. (Box 21)
  - Owen, Iva A. (Box 21)
  - Parrot, Grace A. (Box 21)
  - Pattison, Ernestine (Box 21)
  - Peck, Rachel K. (Box 21)
  - Peyser, Ethel R. (Box 21)
  - Pinckard, Marie L. (Box 21)
  - Pitou, Elsie E. (Box 21)
  - Platt, Henrietta (Box 21)
  - Powell, Elizabeth L. (Box 21)
  - Pratt, Carrie L. (Box 21)
  - Pratt, Mary A. (Box 21)
  - Price, Lucy Jeanne C. (Box 21)
  - Quinn, Mabel A. (Box 21)
  - Rand, Margaret (Box 21)
  - Raynor, Nina F.0 (Box 21)
  - Reed, Mary C. (Box 21)
  - Reiley, Claire L. (Box 21)
  - Reiner, Ada M. (Box 21)
  - Rhone, Alice B. (Box 21)
  - Richardson, Grace H. (Box 21)
  - Richardson, Jessie C. (Box 21)
  - Saltonstall, Lillian M. (Box 21)
  - Sample, Grace A. (Box 21)
  - Scott, Adelaide L. (Box 21)
  - Sealy, Caroline (Box 21)
  - Shaw, Edith Whitney (Box 21)
  - Shepard, D. Alsena (Box 21)
  - Sherry, Susan A. (Box 21)
  - Shillito, Julia B. (Box 21)
  - Shipp, Margaret M. (Box 21)
  - Simon, Mary N. (Box 21)
  - Slaughter, Carrie R. (Box 21)
  - Slaught, Helen A. (Box 21)
  - Smith, Helen A. (Box 21)
  - Smith, Marda K. (Box 21)
  - Smith, Ruth P. (Box 21)
  - Smyth, Sarah D. (Box 21)
  - Snyder, Hallie N. (Box 21)
  - Spencer, Irma M. (Box 21)
  - Spencer, Martha S. (Box 21)
  - Spohr, Ethel M. (Box 22)
  - Spratt, Grace (Box 22)
  - Starr, Margaret G. (Box 22)
  - Steele, Mary B. (Box 22)
  - Steelman, Marjory (Box 22)
  - Stewart, A. Eloise (Box 22)
  - Straight, Hazel H. (Box 22)
  - Street, Bertha M. (Box 22)
  - Street, Elizabeth (Box 22)
  - Street, Emeline A. (Box 22)
  - Swift, Hilda V. (Box 22)
  - Sykes, Katherine B. (Box 22)
  - Taber, Mary F. (Box 22)
  - Talbot, Lucile (Box 22)
  - Tallant, Edith (Box 22)
  - Taylor, Helen D. (Box 22)
  - Thompson, M. Irene (Box 22)
  - Thomson, Mary B. (Box 22)
  - Topping, Mary M. (Box 22)
  - Tucker, Margaret (Box 22)
  - Tuttle, Annie D. (Box 22)
  - Underhill, Ruth Murray (Box 22)
  - Vermilyea, Helen F. (Box 22)
  - Viele, Lois J. (Box 22)
  - Vortriede, Helen A. (Box 22)
  - Wandel, L. Alberta (Box 22)
  - Ward, Anne V. (Box 22)
  - Ware, Jeannette H. (Box 22)
  - Warner, C. Lillian (Box 22)
  - Waterman, Grace (Box 22)
  - Watson, Stella E. (Box 22)
  - Webster, Alice C. (Box 22)
  - Wheeler, Kate P. (Box 22)
  - White, Helen H. (Box 22)
  - White, Mary I. (Box 22)
  - Wiggin, Elizabeth M. (Box 22)
  - Williams, Louise L. (Box 22)
  - Wilson, Jean B. (Box 22)
  - Wilson, May E. (Box 22)
  - Worthington, Daisy L. (Box 22)
  - Wright, A. Bailey (Box 22)
  - Wright, Esther (Box 22)
  - Wright, Mira V. (Box 22)
  - Wrisley, Laura Adelaide (Box 22)
  - Yerex, Gertrude A. (Box 22)
  - Zacher, Madolin R. (Box 22)
- Class of 1906
  - Adams, Eleanor F. (Box 22)
  - Adsit, R. Lionne (Box 22)
  - Aldrich, Louise A. (Box 22)
  - Allen, Annette E. (Box 22)
  - Alvord, Edith H. (Box 22)
  - Ambuhl, Florence Lucina (Box 22)
  - Ashmore, Edith (Box 22)
  - Auringer, Jessie (Box 22)
  - Axtell, Darlene D. (Box 22)
  - Backus, Hazel E. (Box 22)
  - Baldwin, Mabel H. (Box 22)
  - Baldwin, Nina Kent (Box 22)
  - Barnes, Charlotte L. (Box 22)
  - Beales, Angela W. (Box 22)
  - Bennett, Cora E. (Box 22)
  - Borg, Edith D. (Box 22)
  - Borg, Elsoe H. (Box 22)
  - Bowen, H. Marguerite (Box 22)
  - Bradfield, Helen C. (Box 22)
  - Bribach, Ruth L. (Box 22)
  - Brooks, Marjorie E. (Box 22)
  - Brotherton, Nina C. (Box 22)
  - Brown, Bertha (Box 22)
  - Brown, Margaret (Box 22)
  - Brumback, Blanche C. (Box 22)
  - Buffington, Eliza (Box 22)
  - Burlingame, Amy (Box 22)
  - Burr, Dorothy (Box 22)
  - Burton, Margaret E. (Box 22)
  - Buxton, Alice G. (Box 22)
  - Campbell, Annie D. (Box 22)
  - Campbell, Helen (Box 22)
  - Cantlon, Katharine D. (Box 22)
  - Carey, Mary T. (Box 22)
  - Campbell, Katharine Elsie (Box 22)
  - Chandler, Elizabeth J. (Box 22)
  - Chilberg, Mabel (Box 22)
  - Clark, Louise (Box 22)
  - Collier, Edith L. (Box 22)
  - Collier, Elizabeth B. (Box 22)
  - Congdon, Laura (Box 22)
  - Connell, Marion (Box 22)
  - Converse, Rose I. (Box 22)
  - Cooley, L. Esther (Box 22)
  - Comstock, Harriet J. (Box 22)
  - Croll, Rebecca B. (Box 22)
  - Cuddleback, Elizabeth M. (Box 22)
  - Cumpson, Helen (Box 22)
  - Dallas, Mary (Box 22)
  - Dalton, Grace Eads (Box 22)
  - Davey, Ruth L. (Box 22)
  - Davis, Florence Anna (Box 22)
  - Davis, Laura Austin (Box 22)
  - DePuy, Florence G. (Box 22)
  - Dietzman, Anna Priest (Box 22)
  - Dimock, Mary J. (Box 22)
  - Dixon, Edith M. (Box 22)
  - Douglas, Myra Harris (Box 22)
  - Duke, Sara C. (Box 22)
  - Dunwell, Elsie (Box 22)
  - Durrin, Elizabeth (Box 22)
  - Eckhart, Dorothy M. (Box 22)
  - Elwell, Marion F. (Box 22)
  - Evans, Anne M. (Box 22)
  - Evans, Elizabeth M. (Box 22)
  - Evans, Marguerite C. (Box 22)
  - Everman, Edith C. (Box 22)
  - Fair, Ethel M. (Box 22)
  - Farrar, C. Ethel (Box 22)
  - Ferris, Evelyn M. (Box 22)
  - Ferriss, Bessie H. (Box 22)
  - Fink, Cary (Box 22)
  - Fisher, Aimee W. (Box 22)
  - Fitch, Marion (Box 22)
  - Fort, Justine Pellet (Box 22)
  - Ford, Emily V. (Box 22)
  - Fosdick, Edith W. (Box 22)
  - Fraissinet, Linda (Box 22)
  - French, Barbara (Box 22)
  - Frenzel, Caroline E. (Box 22)
  - Cline, Mrs. Elmer L. (Box 22)
  - Fuller, Ada S. (Box 22)
  - Fuller, Alice May (Box 22)
  - Galusha, Ora W. (Box 22)
  - Gilbert, Florence A. (Box 22)
  - Goetchius, Florence M. (Box 22)
  - Gould, Cora Rossiter (Box 22)
  - Gray, Ethel H. (Box 22)
  - Green, Marion A. (Box 22)
  - Griggs, Susan L. (Box 22)
  - Gundlach, Martha C. (Box 22)
  - Hall, Edith G. (Box 22)
  - Halstead, Ruth (Box 22)
  - Hamilton, Mary C. (Box 22)
  - Hamilton, Marion H. (Box 22)
  - Hanley, Charlotte L. (Box 23)
  - Harris, Ella F. (Box 23)
  - Hatch, Laura (Box 23)
  - Hathaway, Anne (Box 23)
  - Hendrickson, Reba C. (Box 23)
  - Henszey, J. Gertrude (Box 23)
  - Hill, Elsie M. (Box 23)
  - Hincken, Elsie O. (Box 23)
  - Holme, Anne W. (Box 23)
  - Holt, Alice E. (Box 23)
  - Howe, Edith (Box 23)
  - Hunt, Barbara (Box 23)
  - Hurlbut, Bertha G. (Box 23)
  - Hutchinson, Hazel (Box 23)
  - Hutchinson, Mary B. (Box 23)
  - Jarnagin, Mary B. (Box 23)
  - Jeffery, Edna (Box 23)
  - Johnston, Hilda (Box 23)
  - Jones, Edith T. (Box 23)
  - Jones, Rebekah T. (Box 23)
  - Kahn, Claribel V. (Box 23)
  - Kauffman, Betsey B. (Box 23)
  - Kautz, Alice M. (Box 23)
  - Kerr, Ada S. (Box 23)
  - Kimball, Nancy B. (Box 23)
  - Kingsbury, Mabel H. (Box 23)
  - Kinne, L. Marie (Box 23)
  - Kinsey, Martha (Box 23)
  - Kirley, Mary P. (Box 23)
  - Klahr, Evelyn G. (Box 23)
  - Knox, Juliet H. (Box 23)
  - Krause, Carlotta F. (Box 23)
  - Larmon, Edith L. (Box 23)
  - Lauder, Julia (Box 23)
  - Lauer, Clara D. (Box 23)
  - Lawrence, Jeannette W. (Box 23)
  - Lewis, Sidney (Box 23)
  - Little, Lida A. (Box 23)
  - Lobingier, Vida (Box 23)
  - Lowry, Ethel C. (Box 23)
  - Lundell, Emma A. (Box 23)
  - Lurie, Frances B. (Box 23)
  - MacDonald, Edith R. (Box 23)
  - MacKellar, Cynthia (Box 23)
  - Madden, Mabel B. (Box 23)
  - Marcus, Hilda H. (Box 23)
  - Marrett, Grace E. (Box 23)
  - Mason, Ruth L. (Box 23)
  - May, Helen B. (Box 23)
  - McCormick, Katharine C. (Box 23)
  - McDonnell, Alberta (Box 23)
  - McGirr, Alice T. (Box 23)
  - McKee, Hazel D. (Box 23)
  - McLure, Elizabeth (Box 23)
  - Mesick, Sara F. (Box 23)
  - Meyer, Florence E. (Box 23)
  - Meyrowitz, Eva H. (Box 23)
  - Miller, Ada L. (Box 23)
  - Millington, Harty (Box 23)
  - Mills, Eleanor (Box 23)
  - Mitchell, Mabel (Box 23)
  - Morris, Florence M. (Box 23)
  - Morris, Katharine McC. (Box 23)
  - Morris, Sarah (Box 23)
  - Morrison, Maude (Box 23)
  - Morse, Marie L. T. (Box 23)
  - Munn, Margaret (Box 23)
  - Munson, Bessie L. (Box 23)
  - Nelson, Florence R. (Box 23)
  - Nevius, Margaret Van D. (Box 23)
  - Noble, Minnie H. (Box 23)
  - Numsen, Margaret T. (Box 23)
  - O’Day, Florence (Box 23)
  - Oldfield, Bertha F. (Box 23)
  - Oldt, Jessie T. (Box 23)
  - Oliphant, Jean A. (Box 23)
  - Ottman, Elizabeth A. (Box 23)
  - Packard, Laura E. (Box 23)
  - Paine, Marion T. (Box 23)
  - Park, Ruth A. (Box 23)
  - Parmly, Katharine D. (Box 23)
  - Parry, Lydia M. (Box 23)
  - Perkins, Jane W. (Box 23)
  - Pierpont, Eleanor B. (Box 23)
  - Platt, M. Alletta (Box 23)
  - Pockman, Helen L. (Box 23)
  - Polk, Elizabeth V. (Box 23)
  - Pownall, Edith M. (Box 23)
  - Price, Helen B. (Box 23)
  - Putnam, Harriett E. (Box 23)
  - Ramsdell, Louise M. (Box 23)
  - Ransom, Ruth (Box 23)
  - Rees, Emma S. (Box 23)
  - Riddle, Ethel M. (Box 23)
  - Ridgway, Inez A. (Box 23)
  - Robinson, Marie E. (Box 23)
  - Robson, Elizabeth A. (Box 23)
  - Rockwood, Margaret A. (Box 23)
  - Roden, Maibelle (Box 23)
  - Rushmore, Elsie M. (Box 23)
  - Saville, Esther (Box 23)
  - Scouton, Hattie A. (Box 23)
  - Searing, Julia (Box 23)
  - Searle, Helen E. (Box 23)
  - Sears, Marion E. (Box 23)
  - Severance, Elizabeth (Box 23)
  - Shannon, Lucy E. (Box 23)
  - Sherwood, Elizabeth B. (Box 23)
  - Sibley, Frances C. (Box 23)
  - Slesinger, Stella (Box 23)
  - Smith, Caroline R. (Box 23)
  - Smith, Ruth E. (Box 23)
  - Steelman, Katherine L. (Box 23)
  - Stewart, Frances J. (Box 23)
  - Streibert, C. Agnes (Box 23)
  - Sweet, Mary C. (Box 23)
  - Talcott, Helen H. (Box 23)
  - Thistle, Margaret B. (Box 23)
  - Towers, Frances T. (Box 23)
  - Townsend, Florence E. (Box 23)
  - Tupper, Margaret (Box 23)
  - Turnbull, Annie G. (Box 23)
  - Turnbull, Mary M. (Box 23)
  - Tuttle, Abbie A. (Box 23)
  - Tuttle, Edith A. (Box 23)
  - Tyler, M. Lucy (Box 23)
  - Tyler, Sarah E. (Box 23)
  - Vaile, Lucretia (Box 23)
  - Van der Veer, Elizabeth K. (Box 23)
  - Van Vleet, Elsa (Box 23)
  - Von Saltza, Elisabeth C. (Box 23)
  - Walbridge, Marie (Box 23)
  - Wales, Theodosia H. (Box 23)
  - Walker, A. Leslie (Box 23)
  - Wallace, Lydia M. (Box 23)
  - Wallach, Annette F. (Box 23)
  - Waller, Margaret L. (Box 23)
  - Warnock, Leonora (Box 23)
  - Warren, Lois (Box 23)
  - Weichert, Anna L. (Box 23)
  - Weil, Elsa I. (Box 24)
  - Weldon, Katharine T. (Box 24)
  - Welwood, Frances A. (Box 24)
  - White, Mabel G. (Box 24)
  - White, Mary E. (Box 24)
  - Wile, Lulu Jean (Box 24)
  - Wilkinson, Ruth Dean (Box 24)
  - Williams, F. Elizabeth (Box 24)
  - Williams, Mabel E. (Box 24)
  - Wilson, Martha E. (Box 24)
  - Wilson, Mary H. (Box 24)
  - Witherbee, Reta (Box 24)
  - Wolfersperger, Leila S. (Box 24)
  - Woodward, Marian E. (Box 24)
  - Woolverton, Primrose (Box 24)
  - Wortendyke, Eleanor E. (Box 24)
  - Wright, Gertrude S. (Box 24)
  - Wright, Julia H. (Box 24)
  - Wright, Mary F. (Box 24)
  - Yerdon, Marion Lucile (Box 24)
  - Zimmerman, Lee (Box 24)
- Class of 1907
  - Affeld, Eda E. (Box 24)
  - Aiken, Margaret H. (Box 24)
  - Allen, Vergie E. (Box 24)
  - Allerton, Edith M. (Box 24)
  - Amen, Elisabeth (Box 24)
  - Amen, Margaret M. (Box 24)
  - Andrus, Ruth (Box 24)
  - Avery, Mary E. (Box 24)
  - Balmer, H. Ruth (Box 24)
  - Bane, Lua M. (Box 24)
  - Barrere, M. Jean (Box 24)
  - Bartlett, Helen Margaret (Box 24)
  - Barton, Thyrza M. (Box 24)
  - Batton, Mary K. (Box 24)
  - Bauman, Evelyn (Box 24)
  - Beckley, Florence (Box 24)
  - Beekman, Idamaye (Box 24)
  - Belding, Alice H. (Box 24)
  - Belknap, Mary C. (Box 24)
  - Bell, Stella B. (Box 24)
  - Benedict, Florence L. (Box 24)
  - Benet, Laura (Box 24)
  - Benton, Harriet J. (Box 24)
  - Bertsch, Florence R. (Box 24)
  - Binns, Laura E. (Box 24)
  - Bleakley, Evelyn E. (Box 24)
  - Bole, Alice A. (Box 24)
  - Borden, Mary Borden (Box 24)
  - Bowman, Elizabeth (Box 24)
  - Bowne, Sarah M. (Box 24)
  - Brace, Mabel (Box 24)
  - Brinsmade, Eleanor G. (Box 24)
  - Brewster, Editha C. (Box 24)
  - Brock, Marion E. (Box 24)
  - Brooke, Louisa (Box 24)
  - Brown, Lulu Florence (Box 24)
  - Brown, May (Box 24)
  - Brumley, Flora Gager (Box 24)
  - Bryner, Edna C. (Box 24)
  - Bunker, Katharine M. (Box 24)
  - Cain, Irma F. (Box 24)
  - Carson, Helen (Box 24)
  - Chapman, Bertha Alice (Box 24)
  - Coats, Marion (Box 24)
  - Collins, Edith (Box 24)
  - Comey, Clara M. (Box 24)
  - Conant, Geneveive (Box 24)
  - Connor, May L. (Box 24)
  - Conover, Elinor (Box 24)
  - Coolidge, Delpha (Box 24)
  - Cory, Edith M. (Box 24)
  - Cosgrove, Margaret (Box 24)
  - Crandall, Mary H. (Box 24)
  - Cranmer, Abby (Box 24)
  - Crawford, Gladys I. (Box 24)
  - Crocker, Gertrude L. (Box 24)
  - Crocker, Pauline (Box 24)
  - Crosby, Ethel (Box 24)
  - Crowell, Ruth (Box 24)
  - Cutler, Ruth E. (Box 24)
  - Cutting, Ellen A. (Box 24)
  - Darrow, Edith Mabel (Box 24)
  - Deacon, Virginia C. S. (Box 24)
  - Decker, Eleanor L. (Box 24)
  - Dow, Abbie M. (Box 24)
  - Downer, Elizabeth (Box 24)
  - Drake, Helen A. (Box 24)
  - Draper, E. Adelaide (Box 24)
  - Dunstan, Emma H. (Box 24)
  - Durbridge, Gwendoline (Box 24)
  - Easton, Florence L. (Box 24)
  - Ebel, Harriet E. (Box 24)
  - Edgcomb, Olive B. (Box 24)
  - Edmands, Violet (Box 24)
  - Fisher, Harriet P. (Box 24)
  - Fisher, Mary E. (Box 24)
  - Flett, Helen Robertson (Box 24)
  - Fritz, Mildred R. (Box 24)
  - Fuller, Paula E. (Box 24)
  - Gabriel, Alpha E. (Box 24)
  - Gardner, Martha (Box 24)
  - Garson, Alice (Box 24)
  - Getman, Frances E. (Box 24)
  - Glaeser, Ida L. (Box 24)
  - Glanville, Eleanor M. (Box 24)
  - Glenn, Helen M. (Box 24)
  - Goodrich, Elizabeth E. (Box 24)
  - Goodyear, M. Amelia (Box 24)
  - Goring, Ethel M. (Box 24)
  - Gould, Jessie G. (Box 24)
  - Gow, Lucy (Box 24)
  - Grant, Alice M. (Box 24)
  - Greenwood, Marion M. (Box 24)
  - Gregg, Florence M. (Box 24)
  - Haines, Faith H. (Box 24)
  - Hamber, Claudine C. (Box 24)
  - Hamburger, Hattie (Box 24)
  - Hamilton, Fannie M. (Box 24)
  - Hamilton, Vera A. (Box 24)
  - Hanson, Marjorie Des (Box 24)
  - Harris, Florence H. (Box 24)
  - Hart, Helen H. (Box 24)
  - Harvie, Millie D. (Box 24)
  - Hasbrouck, Edna A. (Box 24)
  - Hawley, Helen (Box 24)
  - Hedrick, Laura M. (Box 24)
  - Henney, Eleanor M. (Box 24)
  - Hicks, Joy J. (Box 24)
  - Hiller, Minnie (Box 24)
  - Hinkel, Edith W. (Box 24)
  - Hitchcock, Mary M. (Box 24)
  - Hoag, Ruth (Box 24)
  - Holman, Katharine (Box 24)
  - Hopson, Anne W. (Box 24)
  - Howe, Florence P. (Box 24)
  - Hoye, Buena B. (Box 24)
  - Hubbard, Anne M. (Box 24)
  - Hubbard, Elizabeth V. (Box 24)
  - Hughes, Esther McC. (Box 24)
  - Humstone, L. Virginia (Box 24)
  - Huyler, Alice T. (Box 24)
  - Ingraham, Ruth (Box 25)
  - Ivy, Florence (Box 25)
  - Ivy, Mildred (Box 25)
  - Jackson, Emily (Box 25)
  - Jellenik, Ima E. (Box 25)
  - Jewett, Mary D. (Box 25)
  - Johnson, Anna M. (Box 25)
  - Joseph, Eva (Box 25)
  - Keith, Alice (Box 25)
  - Kennedy, Adelaide (Box 25)
  - King, E. Virginia (Box 25)
  - Kinney, Edith (Box 25)
  - Kiper, Pearl (Box 25)
  - Klotz, Sarah J. (Box 25)
  - Knox, Ruth (Box 25)
  - Lambie, Margaret (Box 25)
  - Landon, Mary L. (Box 25)
  - Lawrence, M. Willis (Box 25)
  - Leal, Mary A. (Box 25)